[{"question": "  so ah, your first sexual experience was with a woman?!", "answer": " all right, i was 15, it was my best friend, ruth, and we got drunk on that hard cider, and then suddenly, i don\u0092t know, we were, we were making out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  i mean is that woman capable of talking about anything else but sex?", "answer": " yeah, sure. well y'know, earlier she was talking about geography.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " joey, she was listing the countries she\u0092s done it in.", "answer": " well, i think we all learned something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  hey, you guys! look what i found! look at this!  that\u0092s my mom\u0092s writing! look.", "answer": "  me and frank and phoebe, graduation 1965.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " y'know what that means?", "answer": " that you\u0092re actually 50?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " no-no, that\u0092s not, that\u0092s not me phoebe, that\u0092s her pal phoebe. according to her high school yearbook, they were like b.f.f.  best friends forever.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " that is so cool.", "answer": " i know! so this woman probably could like have all kinds of stories about my parents, and she might even know like where my dad is. so i looked her up, and she lives out by the beach. so maybe this weekend we could go to the beach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " yeah! yeah, we can!", "answer": "  shoot! i can\u0092t go, i have to work!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " that\u0092s too bad.", "answer": "  ohh, big, fat bummerrr.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " so great! okay! tomorrow we\u0092re gonna drive out to montauk.", "answer": " hey, bonnie had sex there!  opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  would you look at them. am i ever gonna find a boyfriend again? i gonna die an old maid.", "answer": " you\u0092re not gonna die an old maid, maybe an old spinster cook.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  thanks!", "answer": " hey now besides, if worst comes to worst, i\u0092ll be your boyfriend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " yeah right.", "answer": " why is that so funny?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " you made a joke right? so i laughed.", "answer": " ha-ha-ha. a little to hard. what am i not ah, boyfriend material?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " okay, so we\u0092ve established my name, and hit me. but theoretically y'know, i mean say we weren\u0092t friends, say it\u0092s a blind date. i show up at your door, and i\u0092m like  \u0093hey, nice to meet, ya. hey, oh-hey.\u0094", "answer": " well i\u0092d probably be scared of a guy using a fake voice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " oh, hey! oh good, you brought food!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s just my luggage.  chandler, monica, and joey: hey!!", "answer": " woo-hoo! all right! yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " oh, i am having the best karma this week. first, i find this woman who knew my parents, and then my client with the fuzzy back gives me his beach house.", "answer": " yeah? what about ah, that bike messenger you hit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh, i wasn\u0092t talking about his karma.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey-hey, check out the hat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " what a minute, i know that hat! i was taken aboard that hat! they did experiments on me! i can\u0092t have children!!", "answer": " seriously, where did you get the hat?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " ross gave it to me.", "answer": " yeah, i think she looks good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " ohh, thank you.", "answer": " buy it for ya, or win it for ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well excuse me, my fashion-impaired friends, i am here to tell you that hats are back.", "answer": " and this time, they\u0092ve ganged up to form one giant, super hat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " go, go, go!", "answer": " oh yeah, now everybody wants to be under this hat!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oy!!", "answer": " what\u0092s with all this sand?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh, yeah, bob said there might be flood damage.", "answer": " yeah, either that, or he has a really big cat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " well, yes, it\u0092s kind\u0092ve an unusual house. it has umm, three beautiful bedrooms and ah, no baths. but y'know, the ocean is right there.", "answer": "  knock, knock, knock.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": "  are you ah, phoebe abott?", "answer": " ahh, yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " hi phoebe abott, i\u0092m your best friends daughter!", "answer": " you\u0092re erwin\u0092s daughter?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " no, i-i mean your-your old best friend, here.  lily, from high school. remember?", "answer": " oh gosh, lily, yes. of course i remember lily. i... then you must be?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  phoebe.  phoebe. phoebe, yeah. she named me after you i guess.", "answer": " uh-huh. wow! well, look! there\u0092s frank.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " yes!! yes! yes! yes!! that\u0092s my dad, that\u0092s frank! yeah! i\u0092m sorry i\u0092m getting all flingy.", "answer": " take it easy--if you want, there\u0092s cookies on the counter, or, or--sangria!  i can make sangria!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " no-no, sorry. cookies are good, thanks.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  well, so, umm, anyway umm, i\u0092ve been, i\u0092ve been looking for my father, and umm, have you heard from him, or seen him?", "answer": " oh no, i-i\u0092m sorry, i guess we lost track of everybody after high school.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": "  oh, okay. well, so tell me everything about my parents. everything.", "answer": " ohh, well. y'know we were always together, in fact the had a nickname for the three of us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, what? what was it?", "answer": " the three losers. oh, poor lily.  ohh, y'know i-i heard about what happened, that must have been just terrible for you, losing your mother that way.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  hey, y'know what a really good rainy day game is?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " i mean naked game. strip poker, we should totally play strip poker.", "answer": " no, no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " what are you crazy?!", "answer": " come on! when you go away, you-you have to play, it\u0092s like a law!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  allll done!", "answer": " aww, thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " no-o-o!  no way!", "answer": " come on, please?! i\u0092m boredddd! you let me do it once before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " yeah well, if ah, if that\u0092s the rule this weekend...  no!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " get away!", "answer": " just once!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " stay away!", "answer": " take it like a man, ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  no!  no!", "answer": " oh, come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  oh, hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " oh, so, how are we doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " bored and bored!", "answer": " hey, you know what naked card game is never boring?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " noo!!", "answer": "  so what\u0092s phoebe like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " i\u0092m kind, caring, and sweet. what\u0092s monica like?", "answer": " ah no, the other phoebe, the one you went to go see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " ohh, i think she knows where my dad is.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " oh well, where is he?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " she was acting, she was pretending like she hasn\u0092t heard from him on years, but i found this picture on her fridge, and look ! isn\u0092t this what he would look like now?", "answer": "  totally familiar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh, yeah.", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " well, why would she lie to you?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, but we\u0092re having dinner tomorrow night, so i figured, she\u0092s gonna tell me then. y'know maybe she just wanted to give him time to, buy me presents, i don\u0092t know! so, you\u0092re all bored?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " ohh!!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092m gonna close my eyes and point to someone, and you, whoever i point has to come up with something fun for us to do, and we have to do it.", "answer": " okay, all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " fan out! fan out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " okay, umm, we all have to play strip poker.", "answer": "  oh yes!!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " strip happy days game?", "answer": " yeah, well, i couldn\u0092t find any cards, so it was either this or strip bag of old knitting stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay,  fonzy gives you two thumbs up, collect two cool points. yeah.", "answer": " monica, if you get five cool points, you get to make somebody take off one item of clothing. it hasn\u0092t happened yet, but we\u0092re all very excited.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " okay, come on!  daddy needs a new pair of electromagnetic microscopes for the prehistoric forensics department!   okay.  take pinky tuscadero up to inspiration point, collect three cool points!! yeah! which gives me five, and let\u0092s see who is gonna lose their clothes. ummmm, i think i pick our strip poker sponsor mr. joey tribianni.", "answer": " woo-hooooo!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " all right, relax. it\u0092s just a shoe.", "answer": " wooooo!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  okay, your band is playing at arnold\u0092s, collect three cool points. which means, i have five, and that means i get joey\u0092s boxers!", "answer": " fine. gang up on me! i got you all right where i want you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " come on, take \u0091em off!!", "answer": " actually, y'know it\u0092s kinda cold, so how about i keep my boxers on, and give you all a peek at the good stuff?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " whoa, hey! what are doing? trying to get me drunk?", "answer": " i\u0092m just making margaritas.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " i think i\u0092ll help her out.   what is going on here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " you painting his toenails?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh, come on!", "answer": " chasing him all around the room?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " monica, please?", "answer": " he\u0092s totally flirting with you too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!  hi bonnie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " hi! my boss let me off early, so i took the train.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " what are you guys doing?!", "answer": " we\u0092re playing strip happy days game!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " so, you still don\u0092t think i\u0092m boyfriend material?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i saw you checking me out during the game last night.", "answer": " you didn\u0092t even take off your pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " yeah, well, lucky for you.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know.", "answer": "  well! is everybody else having just the best time?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " after he passed out, we put the sand around him to keep him warm.", "answer": " well i assume the ah, happy couple isn\u0092t up yet. did you guys hear them last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " good morning.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey! how did everybody sleep?", "answer": " oh, great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " like a log. ross and bonnie: us too.", "answer": " i\u0092m going for a walk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " hey, what happened to you?", "answer": " oh, ah nothin\u0092. i just felt like hangin\u0092 out here and reading.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, the water was sooo great! we jumped off this pier and my suit came off.", "answer": " ohhhh, sorry i missed that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " yeah, joey and chandler sure are funny.", "answer": " ohh-ha-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i think i brought back half of the beach in my hair. it was so much easier when i used to shave my head.", "answer": " y'know, i gotta tell ya, i just loved your look when you were bald.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " because i think about shaving it all off again sometime.", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " i mean you definitely should do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " y'know what, i should do it.", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yeah, thank you rachel, you are soo cool.", "answer": " awww, stop. come on. now go shave that head!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " what\u0092s the matter, pheebs?", "answer": " she cancelled! my namesake cancelled on me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " yeah, she clamed she had to go out of town suddenly. she\u0092s avoiding me, she doesn\u0092t want to tell me where my father is. she knows, and she won\u0092t tell me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " aww pheebs, that sucks!", "answer": " yeah, well, don\u0092t \u0093aww pheebs, that sucks!\u0094 me yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " where ya going?", "answer": " well, she\u0092s out of town so, there\u0092s gotta be something in her house that tells me where my father is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " uh, pheebs, some people call that breaking and entering.", "answer": " well, are any of those people here?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " oh, no!! no, no!", "answer": " okay, look i-i-i do something nice, okay? i\u0092ll-i\u0092ll fill her ice trays.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hey, everybody!", "answer": " wow!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " you wanna touch it?", "answer": " nooo, but it, but it\u0092s great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " come on, touch it!", "answer": " okay.  you can feel all the bones in your skull.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " i was having a little chat with ah, bonnie, and ah, guess what, she-she happened to bring up y'know, who was behind the um, whole head shaving idea, and now, who was it? oh, that\u0092s right, that\u0092s right, it was you!", "answer": " that was her idea, i just gave her a nudge.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " she said you gave her the razor!", "answer": "  hey guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so, anyone up for a midnight dip in the ocean?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " ahh, no, i\u0092m good.", "answer": " okay, i\u0092ll see you in a bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " okay, have fun! wooo!!", "answer": " come on see, she doesn\u0092t look that bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " you can see the moonlight bouncing off her head! what the hell were you thinking?!!", "answer": " i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " you don\u0092t know?! rach, you balded my girlfriend!", "answer": " all right! ross, do you think it\u0092s easy for me to see you with somebody else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " y'know, hey! you\u0092re the one who ended it, remember?", "answer": " yeah, because i was mad at you, not because i stopped loving you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " you still love me?", "answer": " noo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " you still love me.", "answer": " oh, y-yeah, so, you-you love me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " noo, nnnnn. what does this mean? what do you, i mean do you wanna, get back together?", "answer": " noo! maybe! i, i don\u0092t know. ross, i still can\u0092t forgive you for what you did, i can\u0092t, i just, but sometimes when i\u0092m with you i just, i feel so...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i just, i feel, i-i just...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " i feel...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " but i made cards!!", "answer": " well! good night.  i\u0092m going upstairs. joey and chandler: g\u0092night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " no! no!! it\u0092s me! it\u0092s me! i-i didn\u0092t want to make any noise!", "answer": " then don't break in!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " what are you doing here?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i-i, came to fill your ice cube trays.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " umm, okay, okay, look. i took this picture from your fridge. okay, because i know that this is my father. yeah, this is frank buffay and you are standing right there next to him. now, look i deserve to know where i came from. all right? so if you can help me find my father then you should! otherwise, you\u0092re just mean!  so, just tell me the truth!", "answer": " all right, the man in the picture is chuck magioni.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " my father is chuck magioni?", "answer": " no, no, that\u0092s just chuck magioni, i-i sold him a house last year! and i\u0092m very sorry, but i don\u0092t know where your father is, and that\u0092s the truth.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " but umm, you\u0092re right. i think that a person should know where they come from. wh-which is why i ah,  ahh,  okay. i\u0092m your mother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " heh?", "answer": " y'know i wanted to tell you yesterday, but i just, i kinda felt all floopy, and...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i\u0092m telling ya, you guys are totally getting back together!", "answer": " that\u0092s not true! her, she doesn\u0092t even know what she wants! rachel\u0092s still mad about the whole thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " okay, then you gotta back away, all right? you don\u0092t need that kind\u0092ve hurt. take it from a guy who\u0092s never had a long term relationship......", "answer": " i know, but ahhhhhh!! i really wanna go up there and finish that kiss!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " ahhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " you guys, the water\u0092s great. you should really go in.", "answer": " oh, ahh, no thanks, i just had an m&m.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " okay, well g\u0092night.", "answer": " good night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": "  don\u0092t be too long.", "answer": " okey-dokey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " there is not one hair on that head.", "answer": " hey, it\u0092ll grow back, right? and she-she\u0092s really fun, and she\u0092s cool, and-and i\u0092m finally moving on. y'know? i mean getting over rachel was so , y'know? y'know, and i\u0092m finally feeling sane again. and now if i go up there, and-and i kiss her, and, gooood i wanna kiss her, and-and-and it doesn\u0092t work out, right? do i really wanna put myself through that again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " so let me get this straight. if you go with bonnie tonight, you\u0092re doing the smart, healthy thing and moving on.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": "  hi there.", "answer": " that\u0092s that weird voice again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep25.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}]